export default data = [
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'book'?",
    options: ["/bʊk/", " /bʊt/", "/bɔk/", "/buːk/"],
    correct_option: "/bʊk/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'seat'?",
    options: ["/sit/", "/siːt/", "/sʊt/", "/seɪt/"],
    correct_option: "/siːt/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'think'?",
    options: ["/θɪnk/", "/θiːnk/", "/tɪnk/", "/tiːnk/"],
    correct_option: "/θɪnk/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'church'?",
    options: ["/tʃɜːrtʃ/", "/tʃɜːtʃ/", "/tiːnk/", "/tʃʌrtʃ/"],
    correct_option: "/tʃɜːtʃ/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'guitar'?",
    options: ["/ɡɪtɑr/", "/ɡɪtʊr/", "/ɡɪtər/", "/ɡɪtɔr/"],
    correct_option: "/ɡɪtɑr/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'boat'?",
    options: ["/boʊt/", "/beʊt/", "/bɔt/", "/baʊt/"],
    correct_option: "/boʊt/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'measure'?",
    options: ["/meʒər/", "/meʃər/", "/mɛʒər/", "/mɛʃər/"],
    correct_option: "/meʃər/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'yellow'?",
    options: ["/jɛloʊ/", "/jɛləʊ/", "/jɛlɔ/", "/jɛlʌw/"],
    correct_option: "/jɛləʊ/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'sauce'?",
    options: ["/sɔs/", "/soʊs/", "/sɑs/", "/saʊs/"],
    correct_option: "/saʊs/",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the IPA transcription for the word 'feather'?",
    options: ["/fɛðər/", "/fɛθər/", "/fɛðɜr/", "/fɛθɜr/"],
    correct_option: "/fɛðər/",
  },
];
